{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098180498","data":{"timestamp":" 947098180498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098187469","data":{"timestamp":" 947098187468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098198865","data":{"timestamp":" 947098198864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098199367","data":{"timestamp":" 947098199367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098200060","data":{"timestamp":" 947098200060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098201213","data":{"timestamp":" 947098201212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" ANALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098207670","data":{"timestamp":" 947098207670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" START_KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098208583","data":{"timestamp":" 947098208583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098209813","data":{"timestamp":" 947098209812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098210570","data":{"timestamp":" 947098210570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098212977","data":{"timestamp":" 947098212977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098216685","data":{"timestamp":" 947098216685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098225000","data":{"timestamp":" 947098225000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098227639","data":{"timestamp":" 947098227639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098228613","data":{"timestamp":" 947098228613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098229177","data":{"timestamp":" 947098229177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098231317","data":{"timestamp":" 947098231317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098233140","data":{"timestamp":" 947098233140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098235247","data":{"timestamp":" 947098235247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098237145","data":{"timestamp":" 947098237145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098237668","data":{"timestamp":" 947098237668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098238454","data":{"timestamp":" 947098238454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098239842","data":{"timestamp":" 947098239841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098241854","data":{"timestamp":" 947098241853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098242154","data":{"timestamp":" 947098242154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098243752","data":{"timestamp":" 947098243752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098245177","data":{"timestamp":" 947098245176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098247666","data":{"timestamp":" 947098247665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098248867","data":{"timestamp":" 947098248866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098249380","data":{"timestamp":" 947098249379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098250073","data":{"timestamp":" 947098250072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098253420","data":{"timestamp":" 947098253420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098258009","data":{"timestamp":" 947098258009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098258112","data":{"timestamp":" 947098258112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098261956","data":{"timestamp":" 947098261956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098263454","data":{"timestamp":" 947098263454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098264167","data":{"timestamp":" 947098264167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098266119","data":{"timestamp":" 947098266118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098266573","data":{"timestamp":" 947098266573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098267375","data":{"timestamp":" 947098267375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098269106","data":{"timestamp":" 947098269106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098270633","data":{"timestamp":" 947098270633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098271568","data":{"timestamp":" 947098271567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098272259","data":{"timestamp":" 947098272258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" START_MSICHANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098273541","data":{"timestamp":" 947098273541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098274154","data":{"timestamp":" 947098274154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" START_AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098275188","data":{"timestamp":" 947098275187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098277118","data":{"timestamp":" 947098277117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098277873","data":{"timestamp":" 947098277872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098278425","data":{"timestamp":" 947098278424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098279244","data":{"timestamp":" 947098279243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098280212","data":{"timestamp":" 947098280211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098281653","data":{"timestamp":" 947098281653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098282768","data":{"timestamp":" 947098282768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098282953","data":{"timestamp":" 947098282953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098283465","data":{"timestamp":" 947098283465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098284701","data":{"timestamp":" 947098284701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098286623","data":{"timestamp":" 947098286622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098287115","data":{"timestamp":" 947098287114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098287757","data":{"timestamp":" 947098287756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098289232","data":{"timestamp":" 947098289231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" ANACHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098291020","data":{"timestamp":" 947098291020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098291297","data":{"timestamp":" 947098291297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098291916","data":{"timestamp":" 947098291916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098292760","data":{"timestamp":" 947098292759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" START_ANACHEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098293489","data":{"timestamp":" 947098293489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098295234","data":{"timestamp":" 947098295233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098297206","data":{"timestamp":" 947098297206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098297923","data":{"timestamp":" 947098297923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098299197","data":{"timestamp":" 947098299197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098300509","data":{"timestamp":" 947098300509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098302259","data":{"timestamp":" 947098302259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098302657","data":{"timestamp":" 947098302656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098303777","data":{"timestamp":" 947098303777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098304903","data":{"timestamp":" 947098304902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098306840","data":{"timestamp":" 947098306840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098307323","data":{"timestamp":" 947098307323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098307834","data":{"timestamp":" 947098307833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098308337","data":{"timestamp":" 947098308337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098310172","data":{"timestamp":" 947098310171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098311749","data":{"timestamp":" 947098311749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098311752","data":{"timestamp":" 947098311752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098312264","data":{"timestamp":" 947098312263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098313214","data":{"timestamp":" 947098313213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098314264","data":{"timestamp":" 947098314263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098315742","data":{"timestamp":" 947098315741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098317233","data":{"timestamp":" 947098317232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098319965","data":{"timestamp":" 947098319965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098320478","data":{"timestamp":" 947098320478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098321623","data":{"timestamp":" 947098321623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" WANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098322448","data":{"timestamp":" 947098322447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098323402","data":{"timestamp":" 947098323401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098325067","data":{"timestamp":" 947098325066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098325663","data":{"timestamp":" 947098325663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098326046","data":{"timestamp":" 947098326046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" START_WANASOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098327078","data":{"timestamp":" 947098327077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098328755","data":{"timestamp":" 947098328754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098329035","data":{"timestamp":" 947098329035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" START_KIMYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098330148","data":{"timestamp":" 947098330147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098331563","data":{"timestamp":" 947098331562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098333917","data":{"timestamp":" 947098333917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098334644","data":{"timestamp":" 947098334644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098335861","data":{"timestamp":" 947098335860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098336997","data":{"timestamp":" 947098336996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098338655","data":{"timestamp":" 947098338655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098339192","data":{"timestamp":" 947098339192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098339592","data":{"timestamp":" 947098339592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" START_ANAHISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098341727","data":{"timestamp":" 947098341727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098343193","data":{"timestamp":" 947098343193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098345950","data":{"timestamp":" 947098345950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098347054","data":{"timestamp":" 947098347054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" ANAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098347716","data":{"timestamp":" 947098347715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098350136","data":{"timestamp":" 947098350135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098358992","data":{"timestamp":" 947098358992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098360765","data":{"timestamp":" 947098360765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098362790","data":{"timestamp":" 947098362789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098363055","data":{"timestamp":" 947098363054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098377789","data":{"timestamp":" 947098377788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 502044e5-26ea-447c-8f61-dea10aa60c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098396970","data":{"timestamp":" 947098396970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098403280","data":{"timestamp":" 947098403280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098404457","data":{"timestamp":" 947098404457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098408368","data":{"timestamp":" 947098408368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyumba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyu"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098414621","data":{"timestamp":" 947098414621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyumba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nyu"," userResponse":" nyu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098415596","data":{"timestamp":" 947098415596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyumba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098422786","data":{"timestamp":" 947098422786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098423876","data":{"timestamp":" 947098423876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098428255","data":{"timestamp":" 947098428254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mamba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098429147","data":{"timestamp":" 947098429146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mamba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098434769","data":{"timestamp":" 947098434769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dudu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098435601","data":{"timestamp":" 947098435601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dudu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098439479","data":{"timestamp":" 947098439479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ya"," userResponse":" ya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098440396","data":{"timestamp":" 947098440396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_yai"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098444050","data":{"timestamp":" 947098444050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" ngwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098448969","data":{"timestamp":" 947098448969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098450278","data":{"timestamp":" 947098450278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngwa"," userResponse":" ngwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098455109","data":{"timestamp":" 947098455108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_duma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098456409","data":{"timestamp":" 947098456409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_duma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098465891","data":{"timestamp":" 947098465890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098467290","data":{"timestamp":" 947098467290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098471786","data":{"timestamp":" 947098471786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098472594","data":{"timestamp":" 947098472594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098474174","data":{"timestamp":" 947098474174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098483801","data":{"timestamp":" 947098483800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098493783","data":{"timestamp":" 947098493782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098503482","data":{"timestamp":" 947098503482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098512096","data":{"timestamp":" 947098512096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" f3629b27-fcb5-4942-8ab3-531809f8b515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098528318","data":{"timestamp":" 947098528318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098528921","data":{"timestamp":" 947098528919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098529849","data":{"timestamp":" 947098529848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098529993","data":{"timestamp":" 947098529993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098530708","data":{"timestamp":" 947098530708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098531405","data":{"timestamp":" 947098531404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098532129","data":{"timestamp":" 947098532129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098532717","data":{"timestamp":" 947098532717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098532950","data":{"timestamp":" 947098532950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098533442","data":{"timestamp":" 947098533441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098542920","data":{"timestamp":" 947098542919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098546669","data":{"timestamp":" 947098546669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098548783","data":{"timestamp":" 947098548783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098551196","data":{"timestamp":" 947098551196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098553016","data":{"timestamp":" 947098553016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098555186","data":{"timestamp":" 947098555185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098557290","data":{"timestamp":" 947098557289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098559561","data":{"timestamp":" 947098559561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098561219","data":{"timestamp":" 947098561219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098563835","data":{"timestamp":" 947098563835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098566645","data":{"timestamp":" 947098566644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098567158","data":{"timestamp":" 947098567157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098567761","data":{"timestamp":" 947098567761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098568565","data":{"timestamp":" 947098568564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098569458","data":{"timestamp":" 947098569457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098573182","data":{"timestamp":" 947098573182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098577033","data":{"timestamp":" 947098577033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098579583","data":{"timestamp":" 947098579582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098589087","data":{"timestamp":" 947098589087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098596865","data":{"timestamp":" 947098596865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098599083","data":{"timestamp":" 947098599083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098599507","data":{"timestamp":" 947098599506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098599619","data":{"timestamp":" 947098599619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098600053","data":{"timestamp":" 947098600053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098600556","data":{"timestamp":" 947098600556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098601329","data":{"timestamp":" 947098601329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098601992","data":{"timestamp":" 947098601992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098611425","data":{"timestamp":" 947098611425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098613752","data":{"timestamp":" 947098613752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098617204","data":{"timestamp":" 947098617204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098625228","data":{"timestamp":" 947098625228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098627129","data":{"timestamp":" 947098627129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098635314","data":{"timestamp":" 947098635314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098639220","data":{"timestamp":" 947098639220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947098639371","data":{"timestamp":" 947098639371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_214924"," gameId":" 9a961025-1201-458a-b1ce-f5821adc212a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}